Apple number 26 is going to be talking
about the process to actually create one
of these apps and once this type of
platform actually exists and I believe
you get a group of people together say
honored people thousand people who share
a similar problem so the divorce people
or people who like to eat food that's
most of us and you find out what is the
problem what stops you from eating
healthy what stops you from eating
cheaply what would you like your food
life to be like and then you can
brainstorm what a perfect app would be
so but included absolutely everything
and sky was the limit never no
technological or monetary restrictions
what would you create as a group and
this can be done in small groups and
then voted on and improved on to make
the best lockdoor in this case you're
just brainstorming so we've got it
together and then vote on the top ones
you absolutely would need down to the
ones that are able to be added on later
and maybe some that probably are never
going to be included in it but finding a
way to filter it down to what needs to
be in it
what's cost effective to be in it then
[Music]
having people in realms create that so
putting mock-ups saying how much it
would cost to actually create it like if
I created it I could make that fifty
thousand and I can make it for ten
thousand my company can make it for a
million whatever it happens to be and
then crowdsourcing the one that we vote
for so maybe we want to make the million
dollar project if you want to make the
ten thousand dollar project crowd just a
crowdsourcing crowdfunding for it so
let's come up with a million dollars a
million people we put in $1 does that
happen I don't know what we all eat so I
think we can find a million people who
eat and want to
have food cue play and efficiently and
so is you going to create the app and
then you have online systems that
monitor it and say who is using it what
is their experience what would make it
better
what should 2 point version 2.0 have and
that is the process to create an app in
two and a half minutes